dinodirect.com 2004-12-27

# About Privacy & Security :

**Our Commitment**  
As part of our commitment to you, our customers, we have published below our privacy and security policies. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. Thank you for putting your trust in us.

**TRUSTe Licensee**  
dynadirect.com, Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. This statement discloses the privacy practices for dynadirect.com. When you visit a Web site displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, you can expect to be notified of: What personally identifiable information of yours is collected; What organization is collecting the information; How the information is used; With whom the information may be shared; What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information; What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the company's control; and How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the [Webmaster](mailto:comments@dynadirect.com). If the Web site has not responded to your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact [TRUSTe](http://truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php?).

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an Email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**Your Information**  
This site uses a secure online order form for customers to purchase products and services. We collect customer contact information, such as Name, Email, Phone Number, and Address, and financial information, such as Credit Card Account Information. Contact information from the order form is only used to process and ship orders to our customers and to get in touch with them when necessary. Financial information collected is used to bill the customer for products and services they have purchased or requested.

A returns form is also available on this site, to offer our customers the convenience of requesting a Return Merchandise Authorization Number (RMA#) for sending product(s) back for replacement, repair or credit. The information collected on this form is used to process the request, and to expedite the returns process. This information includes Customer Name, Phone Number, and Email.

**Changing/Updating Information**  
Customers have the opportunity to update or change their personal and financial information each time an order is placed. Customers can also request changes by contacting Customer Service directly by Email at [service@dynadirect.com](mailto:service@dynadirect.com) or phone at  
1-877-438-3962. dynadirect.com also offers optional online customer registration, that allows personal information to be edited at anytime through a secured login.

**Security**  
  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All online transactions are handled with industry-standard SSL encryption. When you place an order online, your personal information and credit card information are encrypted (scrambled) using this technology before being sent over the Internet. This makes it virtually impossible for your information to be stolen or intercepted while being transferred through cyberspace (the Internet). When we receive your order, it is kept encrypted until we're ready to process it.

When you proceed to the online checkout, your browser will automatically be switched to the secure server. This can be verified by the "https" displayed in your browsers address field as shown in the image below:

**Yahoo Information**  
This site is hosted by Yahoo!. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Yahoo will also send a customer satisfaction survey to you via Email, if you select this option during checkout. Please see the [Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information.

Yahoo! offers a Buyer Protection Program that protects shoppers utilizing Yahoo! Shopping. Most items purchased through Yahoo! Shopping are covered by this program, which is backed by insurance obtained through Lloyd's of London. For more information on this program [Click Here](http://shopping.yahoo.com/buyer_protection.html).

**Correspondence**  
Once an order has been placed online, customers will receive a confirmation Email with a link to check order status online. If additional information is needed, customers may contact Customer Service via Email at [service@dynadirect.com](mailto:service@dynadirect.com) or by phone at  
1-877-438-3962. dynadirect.com does not send unsolicited (SPAM) Email, rent/sell its Email lists or customer information.

**"Tell a Friend" Email Service**  
dynadirect.com offers a service that will Email a product page and comments to anyone with an Email address. This service allows you to let friends and family know about our great deals and service. We do not collect or store the Email addresses used with this service. Please report any misuse of this service to our [Privacy Officer](mailto:dbolinger@dynadirect-inc.com) immediately.

**Sharing Information**  
dynadirect.com ships product from warehouses all over the country. To fulfill customer orders information such as Customer Name, Address, and Phone Number are transmitted via Email or FAX to the warehouse that ships the product(s) ordered. Financial information collected is never shared with any other branch, office, warehouse, or organization.

dynadirect.com will not disclose any of our customers personal or financial information to third parties other than shipping intermediaries, except when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or to protect the rights or property of dynadirect.com.

**Links and Affiliates**  
This Web site contains links to other website and online stores. Please be aware that our privacy policy does not apply to these linked sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any website. dynadirect.com takes great care in selecting the companies it does business with, and will not promote or represent companies that do not provide customers with the highest level of service.

* * *

**dynadirect.com, Inc.**  
11830 Fishing Point Drive  
Oyster Point Park  
Suite 213  
Newport News, VA 23606  
Toll-Free: (877) 438-3962  
Phone: (757) 873-7675  
Fax: (757) 873-7638
